Register of the Sir Karl Raimund Popper Papers, 1928-1995
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE I, 1932-1987
  - J.C.B. Mohr/Paul Siebeck (Hans Georg Siebeck, Georg Siebeck), re The Poverty of Historicism, The Logic of Scientific Discovery, Die beiden Grundprobleme der Erkenntnistheorie, Conjectures and Refutations.
    Includes correspondence with Oliver E. Ford and Bernd Enders. See also Erik Boettcher and Herr Wienhold
    - 1961 (Box 312, Folder 1)
    - 1965 (Folder 2)
    - 1966 (Folder 3)
    - 1967 (Folder 4)
    - 1968 (Folder 5)
    - 1969 (Folder 6)
    - 1970 (Folder 7)
    - 1971 (Folder 8)
    - 1972 (Folder 9)
    - 1973 (Folder 10)
    - 1974 (Folder 11)
    - 1975 (Folder 12)
    - 1976 (Folder 13)
    - 1977 (Folder 14)
    - 1978 (Folder 15)
    - 1979 (Folder 16)
    - 1980-1984 (Folder 17)
  - Jabs, Arthur, 1978-1985 (Folder 18)
  - Jacob, Francois, 1979 (Folder 19)
  - Jacob, Pierre, 1979-1980 (Folder 20)
  - Jaeger, Hasso, 1965-1966 (Folder 21)
  - Jaeger, Wolfgang, 1972 (Folder 22)
  - Jaki, Stanley L., 1982 (Folder 23)
  - James, D. Marc, 1978-1979 (Folder 24)
  - James, G. D., 1979 (Folder 25)
  - James, Roger, 1973-1985 (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - James Thin Ltd., 1977-1978 (Folder 2)
  - Jammer, Max, 1967-1984 (Folder 3)
  - Janoska, Georg, 1967-1970 (Folder 4)
  - Japan Uni Agency (Hideo Aoki, Kozaburo Yano), 1973-1985, mainly re Unended Quest (Folder 5)
  - Jarvie, Ian Charles, 1957-1984 (Folder 6)
  - Jary, Walther, 1978 (Folder 7)
  - Jeffrey, Richard C., 1970 (Folder 8)
  - Jeffreys, Harold, 1942-1958 (Folder 9)
  - Jewish Year Book, 1969 (Folder 10)
  - Ji, Shu-li, 1982 (Folder 11)
  - John Didier Editions, 1981 (Folder 12)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1979 (Folder 13)
  - John Wiley & Sons Limited, 1983-1984 (Folder 14)
  - Johnson, Barclay D., 1977 (Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Daniel, 1976-1977 (Folder 16)
  - Johnstone, R. Edgeworth, 1971-1983 (Folder 17)
  - Johr, W. A., 1981 (Folder 18)
  - Jonathan Cape Ltd., 1980 (Folder 19)
  - Jones, G. O., 1965-1967 (Folder 20)
  - Jones, P. E., 1970 (Folder 21)
  - Jordan, P., 1935. (Folder 22)
    Includes letter from Frankfurter Zeitung
  - Jorgensen, J., 1935-1946 (Folder 23)
  - Joseph, Kevin, 1977 (Folder 24)
  - Joseph Rowntree Memorial Trust (Robin Guthrie), 1982 (Folder 25)
  - Journal of Industrial Affairs, 1984 (Folder 26)
  - Journal of Philosophy, 1982 (Folder 27)
  - Journal of Symbolic Logic, 1951-1965 (Folder 28)
  - Judge, H. Y., 1960 (Folder 29)
  - Junankar, N. S., 1964 (Folder 30)
  - Jung, Richard, 1983 (Folder 31)
  - Kadlec, Bernard, 1974-1978 (Box 314, Folder 1)
  - Kadlec, Erich, 1974-1985 (Folder 2)
  - Kaestner, Heinrich, 1979-1980 (Folder 3)
  - Kahn, Charles H., 1965-1981 (Folder 4)
  - Kahn-Freund, Otto, 1946 (Folder 5)
  - Kalicki, Jan, 1951 (Folder 6)
  - Kalista, Monika, 1979-1982 (Folder 7)
  - Kalman, Rudolf E., 1983 (Folder 8)
  - Kalmar, Laszlo, 1966-1968 (Folder 9)
  - Kamenka, Eugene, 1969 (Folder 10)
  - Kaneko, Mitsuo, 1984 (Folder 11)
  - Kanitscheider, Bernulf, 1978-1984 (Folder 12)
  - Kannellopoulos, P., re Constantine D. Tsatsos., 1978 (Folder 13)
    Includes letter to Linos Benakis
  - Kaplan, Morton A., 1978-1979 (Folder 14)
  - Kapp, Reginald O., 1952-1957. (Folder 15)
    Includes Karl Popper's typewritten comments on Peter Alexander's review of Reginald O. Kapp's book Mind, Life, and Body
  - Karlan, Daniel M., 1977 (Folder 16)
  - Kary, Michael, 1983-1984 (Folder 17)
  - Kasper, Helmut, 1968-1969 (Folder 18)
  - Karstendiek, Helmut, 1981 (Folder 19)
  - Kathimerimi, 1983 (Folder 20)
  - Katholiek Centrum voor Lectuurinformatie en Bibliotheekvoorziening, 1981 (Folder 21)
  - Katouzian, Homa, 1975-1983 (Folder 22)
  - Kattsoff, L. O., 1949 (Folder 23)
  - Katz, Bernard, 1983 (Folder 24)
  - Kaus, Rainer, 1972 (Folder 25)
  - Kavanagh, H., 1983 (Folder 26)
  - Kekes, John, 1976-1981 (Box 315, Folder 1)
  - Keller, Hannes, 1985 (Folder 2)
  - Kemeny, John G., 1951-1954 (Folder 3)
  - Kendall, Maurice G., 1955-1964 (Folder 4)
  - Kennan, George F., 1984 (Folder 5)
  - Kennet, Wayland, 1981 (Folder 6)
  - Kenny, Anthony J. P., 1984 (Folder 7)
  - Kermode, Frank, 1970 (Folder 8)
  - Keuth, Herbert, 1969-1973 (Folder 9)
  - Khan, R. F., 1961 (Folder 10)
  - Kielwein, R., 1960-1961 (Folder 11)
  - Kiepenheuer & Witsch, 1980 (Folder 12)
  - Kiesewetter, Hubert, 1968-1985 (Folder 13)
  - Kiesslinger, Rudolf, 1983 (Folder 14)
  - Kindler Verlag Zurich, 1981 (Folder 15)
  - King, Edmund J., 1966-1982 (Folder 16)
  - King, Preston, 1961 (Folder 17)
  - Kirchhoff, Joachim, 1983-1985 (Folder 18)
  - Kirchschlager, Rudolf, 1977-1985 (Folder 19)
  - Kirk, G. S., 1959-1965 (Folder 20)
  - Kitchen, Jack, 1953 (Folder 21)
  - Klappholz, Kurt, 1982 (Folder 22)
  - Kleene, Stephen C., 1968 (Folder 23)
  - Klein, Robert F., 1979 (Folder 24)
  - Klemke, E. D., 1974-1979 (Folder 25)
  - Klibansky, Raymond, 1968-1969 (Folder 26)
  - Klose, Dietrich, 1981 (Folder 27)
  - Knaurs Prominentenlexicon, 1980 (Folder 28)
  - Kneale, William C., 1945-1983 (Folder 29)
  - Knox, F., n.d. (Folder 30)
  - Koch, L. E., 1964 (Folder 31)
  - Kochen, Simon, 1973-1982 (Folder 32)
  - Koenne, Werner, 1983 (Folder 33)
  - Koertge, Noretta, 1968-1984 (Folder 34)
  - Koesters, Paul-Heinz, 1980 (Folder 35)
  - Koestler, Arthur, n.d. (Folder 36)
  - Koga, Toyoki, 1973-1983 (Folder 37)
  - Kohl, Helmut, 1977 (Box 316, Folder 1)
  - Kohler, Eckehart, 1968 (Folder 2)
  - Kohn, Hans, 1950-1966 (Folder 3)
  - Kolakowski, Leszek, 1971-1982 (Folder 4)
  - Kolb, Fritz and Martha, 1961-1984. (Folder 5)
    Includes Karl Popper's handwritten and typewritten foreword to Fritz Kolb's book Es kam ganz anders, 1981
  - Kolditz, Wolfgang, 1979-1984 (Folder 6)
  - Koliha, Lothar, 1984 (Folder 7)
  - Koller, Frau, n.d. (Folder 8)
  - Kolnai, Aurel T., 1952-1955 (Folder 9)
  - Komarek, Kurt, 1978 (Folder 10)
  - Komitee zur Organisation eines Osterreichischen Schriftstellerkongresses, 1980 (Folder 11)
  - Kongress fur die Freiheit der Kultur, 1947 (Folder 12)
  - Konig, Heinz, 1981 (Folder 13)
  - Konstanzer Blatter fur Hochschulfragen, 1971 (Folder 14)
  - Koppelmann, Floris, 1980 (Folder 15)
  - Kordig, Carl R., 1980-1981 (Folder 16)
  - Korean Broadcasting System, 1981-1982 (Folder 17)
  - Korn, Peter Jona and Barbara, 1981 (Folder 18)
  - Korner, Stephan, 1957-1981 (Folder 19)
  - Kornhuber, H. H., 1977 (Folder 20)
  - Kosel-Verlag, 1972-1978 (Folder 21)
  - Kothbauer, Hilde, 1972 (Folder 22)
  - Kraft, Julius, 1945-1960. (Folder 23)
    Includes correspondence with Margit Kraft, 1961
  - Kraft, Victor, 1932-1974. (Folder 24)
    Includes correspondence with Eva Frodl-Kraft, 1975
  - Krag (Nina Smolar), 1984 (Folder 25)
  - Krah, Wolfgang, 1972-1975 (Folder 26)
  - Krakau, C. E. T., 1982 (Folder 27)
  - Krassnigg, Albert, 1970. (Box 317, Folder 1)
    Includes Karl Popper's typewritten report entitled "Einige Bemerkungen uber die Wiener Schulreform und ihr Einfluss auf mich," 1970, as well as a letter to Albert Krassnigg's widow, 1971
  - Kratky, Otto, 1980-1985 (Folder 2)
  - Kraus, Michael, 1951 (Folder 3)
  - Kraus, Wolfgang, 1968-1984 (Folder 4)
  - Krausz, Michael, 1960-1985 (Folder 5)
  - Krawietz, Werner, 1976-1977 (Folder 6)
  - Krebs, Greti, 1982 (Folder 7)
  - Krebs, Hans, 1976 (Folder 8)
  - Kreisel, Georg, 1952-1983. (Folder 9)
    Includes Georg Kreisel's typewritten review of A. Mostowski's book Sentences Undecidable in Formalized Arithmetic: An Exposition of the Theory of Kurt Godel, annotated by Karl Popper
  - Kreisky, Bruno, 1972-1982 (Folder 10)
  - Kremenak, Elisabeth K. See Herz, Martin F. and Elisabeth K.
  - Kretschmer, Gerhard, 1965-1968 (Folder 11)
  - Krips, Henry, 1984 (Folder 12)
  - Krohn, Peter L., 1977-1978 (Folder 13)
  - Kroiss, Gerhard, 1981-1984 (Folder 14)
  - Kroy, Moshe, 1970-1979 (Folder 15)
  - Kruger, Lorenz, 1968-1972 (Folder 16)
  - Kuhn, Thomas S., 1965 (Folder 17)
  - Kuipers, Theo A. F., 1978-1983 (Folder 18)
  - Kulmann, Hermann, 1981-1982 (Folder 19)
  - Kulturzeitschrift (Gabriele Pfan), 1979 (Folder 20)
  - Kuppers, Bernd-Olaf, 1983 (Folder 21)
  - Kuppner, Frank, 1983 (Folder 22)
  - Kustannusosakeyhtio Otava, 1965, re The Open Society (Folder 23)
  - Kuswetter, H., 1977 (Folder 24)
  - Kuypers, K., 1970-1983 (Folder 25)
  - Kvan, Eric, 1963-1965 (Folder 26)
  - Kwiatkowski, Gerhard (Bibliographisches Institut), 1978-1979 (Folder 27)
  - Kyburg, Henry E., Jr., 1960-1967. (Folder 28)
    Includes a letter from Sigmund Neumann
  - Kyrkos, Basileiy A., 1974-1985 (Folder 29)
  - Labedz, Leopold, 1973-1980 (Box 318, Folder 1)
  - Lahti, Pekka J., 1984-1985 (Folder 2)
  - Lai, Tyrone, 1968 (Folder 3)
  - Lakatos, Imre
    - Undated (Folder 4)
    - 1959-1963. (Folder 5)
      Includes correspondence with Suresh C. Parikh
    - 1964 (Folder 6)
    - 1965 (Folder 7)
    - 1966 (Folder 8)
    - 1967-1969 (Folder 9)
    - 1970-1973 (Folder 10)
  - Lammer, Meinhart and Traudl, 1968-1974 (Folder 11)
  - Lammer, Robert
    - 1960-1968 (Folder 12)
    - 1970-1978 (Folder 13)
    - 1981-1985 (Folder 14)
  - Lampugnani Nigri Editore, 1972, re The Poverty of Historicism (Folder 15)
  - Lancet, 1978 (Folder 16)
  - Lanczos, Cornelius, 1966-1970 (Folder 17)
  - Lande, Alfred, 1955-1971 (Folder 18)
  - Landsberg, Peter T., 1971-1985 (Folder 19)
  - Lang, C., 1951 (Folder 20)
  - Lange & Springer, 1982 (Folder 21)
  - Laor, Nathaniel, 1983 (Folder 22)
  - Larijani, Sadegh, 1979 (Folder 23)
  - Larsen, Harold, 1945-1946 (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Laszlo, Stephan, 1972 (Folder 2)
  - Laudsberg, Dr., 1957 (Folder 3)
  - Lauener, Henri, 1972-1981 (Folder 4)
  - Launay, Marc and Michelle Brudy de, 1979-1985, re Conjectures and Refutations (Folder 5)
  - Laungani, Pittu, 1978 (Folder 6)
  - Laurence, Alfred Edward, 1968-1970 (Folder 7)
  - Laurikainen, K. V., 1983 (Folder 8)
  - Lauwerys, J. A., 1968-1969 (Folder 9)
  - Lawrence, John, 1978-1979 (Folder 10)
  - Lawrence, Philip J., 1948 (Folder 11)
  - Lawrence Smith Literary Agency (Lawrence Smith), 1955-1973 (Folder 12)
  - Leach, B. Foss, 1980-1983 (Folder 13)
  - Leary, James E., 1960 (Folder 14)
  - Leblanc, Hugues, 1978-1981 (Folder 15)
  - Leeper, G. W., 1974 (Folder 16)
  - Leeuwen, J. van, 1981 (Folder 17)
  - Leinfellner, Werner, 1974 (Folder 18)
  - Lejewski, Czeslaw, 1952-1982 (Folder 19)
  - Leoni, Bruno, 1952-1966 (Folder 20)
  - Leser, Norbert, 1975 (Folder 21)
  - Lessnoff, Michael, 1980 (Folder 22)
  - Letwin, William, 1949 (Folder 23)
  - Leung, Physer, 1980-1984 (Folder 24)
  - Levere, Trevor H., 1977 (Folder 25)
  - Levi, Isaac, 1962-1983 (Folder 26)
  - Levinson, H. B., 1964 (Folder 27)
  - Levinson, Paul, 1978-1983 (Folder 28)
  - Levison, Arnold B., 1963 (Folder 29)
  - Levy, David, 1978 (Folder 30)
  - Levy, H., 1943 (Folder 31)
  - Lewin, Douglas W., 1979 (Folder 32)
  - Lewis, Albert C., 1979-1980 (Folder 33)
  - Lewis, Hywel D., 1983 (Folder 34)
  - Lewis, John, 1972 (Folder 35)
  - Lewis, Thomas T., 1981-1982 (Folder 36)
  - Lewis-Loubignac, Anne, 1982-1983 (Folder 37)
  - Lewy, Casimir, 1946-1982 (Folder 38)
  - Liberal Summer School, 1967 (Folder 39)
  - Librairie Armand Colin (Marianne Veron), 1970-1971, re Conjectures and Refutations (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Librairie Artheme Fayard, 1970-1971, re The Logic of Scientific Discovery (Folder 2)
  - Librairie Ernest Flammarion (Louis Audibert), 1984-1985, re The Poverty of Historicism (Folder 3)
  - Librairie Plon (Helene Bourgeois, Rene Julliard), 1981-1984, re Conjectures and Refutations and The Poverty of Historicism (Folder 4)
  - Library of Science (David Klein). See Basic Books
  - Lieberson, Jonathan, 1982 (Folder 5)
  - Light, Ursula E. K., 1982 (Folder 6)
  - Lindley, T. Foster, 1952 (Folder 7)
  - Lingens, Ella, n.d. (Folder 8)
  - Linguiti, Gennar Luigi, 1976-1977 (Folder 9)
  - Linke, Paul F., 1936-1937 (Folder 10)
  - Linney, D. S., 1952 (Folder 11)
  - Lion, Aline, 1949 (Folder 12)
  - Lippincott, Benjamin E., 1978-1981 (Folder 13)
  - Lipton, Marianne, 1961 (Folder 14)
  - Listener, 1954 (Folder 15)
  - Little, Graham R., 1977-1982 (Folder 16)
  - Little, John, 1980 (Folder 17)
  - Liviana Editrice in Padova, 1970, re Conjectures and Refutations (Folder 18)
  - Livingstone, Angela, 1980 (Folder 19)
  - Lloyd, G. E. R., 1966 (Folder 20)
  - Lock, Andrew, 1979 (Folder 21)
  - Lodynski, Andrej, 1984 (Folder 22)
  - Logan, Ken, 1961-1984 (Folder 23)
  - Loidl, Willi, 1984 (Folder 24)
  - Lombardi, Franco, 1984 (Folder 25)
  - London Review of Books, 1980 (Folder 26)
  - London School of Economics (Walter Adams, Sydney Caine, Huw Wheldon, Ralf Dahrendorf). See also Wasserman, Benno. For pre- correspondence, see COURSE MATERIAL, London School of Economics, Correspondence, 1970
    - 1970-1975 (Folder 27)
    - 1976-1985 (Folder 28)
  - London School of Economics Society, 1980 (Box 321, Folder 1)
  - Lorber, John, 1980 (Folder 2)
  - Lorenz, Ingeborg F. R., 1982 (Folder 3)
  - Lorenz, Konrad Z., 1969-1984. (Folder 4)
    Includes Karl Popper's typewritten tribute to Konrad Lorenz
  - Lorenzen, Hans-Peter, 1970 (Folder 5)
  - Lorenzen, P., 1954-1964 (Folder 6)
  - Lort-Phillips, Patrick, 1978 (Folder 7)
  - Louisiana State University, 1965 (Folder 8)
  - Louisiana State University Press (Beverly Jarrett), 1976 (Folder 9)
  - Lubbe, Hermann, 1972 (Folder 10)
  - Lucas, F. D., 1984 (Folder 11)
  - Luce, A. A., 1968 (Folder 12)
  - Luderssen, Klaus, 1970 (Folder 13)
  - Ludwig-Erhard-Stiftung, 1979-1980 (Folder 14)
  - Lukasiewicz, Jan, 1955 (Folder 15)
  - Lund, Pui-chong and Nellie, 1972-1978 (Folder 16)
  - Lunghi, Sandro, 1981 (Folder 17)
  - Lutfalla, G., 1946 (Folder 18)
  - Lwoff, Professor, 1978 (Folder 19)
  - Lyman, Harry, 1981 (Folder 20)
  - Mabott, J. D., 1952 (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - Macatesta, Michele, 1983 (Folder 2)
  - Macbeth, Norman, 1963-1977. (Folder 3)
    Includes correspondence with Gambit Publishers
  - Mace, C. Alec, See also George Allen & Unwin, 1952. (Folder 4)
  - Machlup, Fritz, 1956-1982 (Folder 5)
  - MacKay, Donald M., 1966-1983 (Folder 6)
  - Mackie, R., 1982 (Folder 7)
  - MacKinnon, Donald M., 1956-1978 (Folder 8)
  - MacKinnon, L., 1983 (Folder 9)
  - MacLane, Professor, 1968 (Folder 10)
  - Maclure, Malcolm, 1984 (Folder 11)
  - Macmillan International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, 1968 (Folder 12)
  - Macmillan London Ltd., 1952-1979 (Folder 13)
  - MacRae, Donald G., 1951-1982 (Folder 14)
  - Magarian, Michael, 1981-1984 (Folder 15)
  - Magee, Bryan
    - Undated (Folder 16)
    - 1958-1959 (Folder 17)
    - 1960-1969 (Folder 18)
    - 1970-1973 (Folder 19)
    - 1974 (Folder 20)
    - 1975-1977 (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - 1978-1979 (Folder 2)
    - 1980-1981 (Folder 3)
    - 1982-1983 (Folder 4)
    - 1984-1985 (Folder 5)
  - Mahieux, Micheline, 1960 (Folder 6)
  - Mahieux, Mr., 1960 (Folder 7)
  - Maier, K. F., 1949 (Folder 8)
  - Maier-Leibnitz, Heinz, 1978-1982 (Folder 9)
  - Makinde, M. Akin, 1972-1984 (Folder 10)
  - Malina, Jaroslav, 1979 (Folder 11)
  - Mall, Jim, 1978 (Folder 12)
  - Manchester University Press, 1983 (Folder 13)
  - Mannheimer Morgen Grossdruckerei und Verlag, 1975, re Mannheimer Forum 75/76 (Folder 14)
  - Manning, C. A. W., 1970 (Folder 15)
  - Mannu, Andrea, 1972-1973 (Box 324, Folder 1)
  - Mansfeld, J., 1971 (Folder 2)
  - Marcus, Ruth Barcan, 1964 (Folder 3)
  - Marek, Johann Christian, 1977-1978 (Folder 4)
  - Margenau, Henry, 1962-1971 (Folder 5)
  - Marhefka, Edmund, 1960-1961 (Folder 6)
  - Marietti Editori, 1970, re The Poverty of Historicism (Folder 7)
  - Mark, Karl, 1982 (Folder 8)
  - Mark Twain Journal, 1977 (Folder 9)
  - Markl, Peter, 1977 (Folder 10)
  - Marks, John, 1978-1983 (Folder 11)
  - Marmet, Paul, 1984 (Folder 12)
  - Marris, Mr., 1970, re Conjectures and Refutations (Folder 13)
  - Marschak, Jacob, 1937-1976 (Folder 14)
  - Marshall, Trevor W., 1983-1985. (Folder 15)
    Includes correspondence between Trevor Marshall and Thomas D. Angelidis and Abner Shimony
  - Martin Santos, Luis, 1968-1971 (Folder 16)
  - Martin Secker & Warburg, 1971 (Folder 17)
  - Martt, Judson, See also Morgan, Richard B., 1975-1985. (Folder 18)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Press, 1970-1971 (Folder 19)
  - Massada Ltd., 1977-1980. (Folder 20)
    Includes correspondence re The Open Society and Philosophia
  - Masse, Pierre, 1982 (Folder 21)
  - Matthews, Bryan, 1957 (Folder 22)
  - Matthiesen, Einar, 1973 (Folder 23)
  - Maurer, Joseph, 1937 (Folder 24)
  - Maxwell, Grover and Mary Lou, 1963-1982 (Folder 25)
  - Maxwell, Nicholas, 1965-1973 (Folder 26)
  - Maycock, R. F., 1982 (Folder 27)
  - Mayerhofer, Josef, 1982-1983 (Folder 28)
  - Mayo, Deborah G., 1983 (Folder 29)
  - Mayper, Stuart A., 1965-1981 (Folder 30)
  - Mayr, Ernst, 1966-1984 (Box 325, Folder 1)
  - Mazzaroli-Gherson, J., 1970-1971 (Folder 2)
  - McCarthy, Patrick J., 1984 (Folder 3)
  - McCausland, Ian, 1980 (Folder 4)
  - McClare, Colin W. F. and Gill, 1965-1978 (Folder 5)
  - McConnell, R. Shean, 1978-1981 (Folder 6)
  - McConnell, Richard B., 1977 (Folder 7)
  - McCrea, William Hunter, 1982, re his review of The Postscript to The Logic of Scientific Discovery (Folder 8)
  - McDonald, Ian, 1977 (Folder 9)
  - McEvoy, Donald P., 1985 (Folder 10)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1968-1972 (Folder 11)
  - McGuinness, Brian, 1981-1984. (Folder 12)
    Includes Karl Popper's writings for the Schlick Festschrift volume
  - McHugh, Paul R., 1985 (Folder 13)
  - McIntyre, Neil, 1980-1983. (Folder 14)
    Includes Karl Popper's holograph "The Very Special Situation of Medical Men and Women"
  - McKeon, Richard P., 1954 (Folder 15)
  - McKinney, J. P., 1960 (Folder 16)
  - McLaren, Donald S., 1977 (Folder 17)
  - McLaren, Robert Bruce, 1981 (Folder 18)
  - McMaster University (Kenneth Blackwell), 1979 (Folder 19)
  - McMullin, Ernan, 1969 (Folder 20)
  - McMurrin, Sterling M., re The Tanner Lectures on Human Values, 1978 (Folder 21)
  - McNelis, Mary J., 1980-1982 (Folder 22)
  - McQuaid, John, 1977-1983 (Folder 23)
  - McWhirter, Norris D., 1980-1982 (Folder 24)
  - Medawar, Peter B.
    - Undated (Folder 25)
    - 1946-1966 (Folder 26)
    - 1970-1974 (Folder 27)
    - 1975-1979 (Folder 28)
    - 1980-1984 (Folder 29)
  - Medical Hypotheses (David F. Horrobin), 1974-1980. (Box 326, Folder 1)
    Includes letter from John C. Eccles to David F. Horrobin
  - Medicine and Mind, 1982 (Folder 2)
  - Meehl, Paul E., 1964-1979 (Folder 3)
  - Megwa, Peter O., 1978-1979 (Folder 4)
  - Mehlberg, Henryk, 1966-1979 (Folder 5)
  - Mehmanesh, Hormoz, 1981-1984 (Folder 6)
  - Meinhardt, H., 1979 (Folder 7)
  - Mejer, Jxrgen, 1971 (Folder 8)
  - Mellone, Dr., 1948 (Folder 9)
  - Mellov, 1984 (Folder 10)
  - Meltzer, Bernard, 1971 (Folder 11)
  - Men of Achievement, 1971 (Folder 12)
  - Menahem, Hanina Ben, 1981-1983 (Folder 13)
  - Menger, Karl, 1951-1980 (Folder 14)
  - Menne, Albert, 1977-1984 (Folder 15)
  - Mensa, 1963-1980 (Folder 16)
  - Mensah, Eugene B., 1983-1984 (Folder 17)
  - Menzl, Walter (Pan~Humanistische Aktion), 1978-1979 (Folder 18)
  - Mercier, Andre, 1946-1949 (Folder 19)
  - Merkel, Reinhard, 1982 (Folder 20)
  - Merklein, Siegfried T., 1981-1983 (Folder 21)
  - Merrill, Daniel D., 1976-1978 (Folder 22)
  - Mertes, Michael, 1977-1979 (Folder 23)
  - Merwe, Alwyn van der, 1982 (Folder 24)
  - Messmer, Bernhard, 1974-1982 (Folder 25)
  - Messner, Johannes, 1981 (Folder 26)
  - Methodology and Science (Piet H. Esser), re "The Present Significance of Two Arguments of Henri Poincare." See also Morscher, Edgar, 1972-1982 (Folder 27)
  - Methuen & Co., 1975-1981 (Folder 28)
  - Mettenheim, Cristoph von, 1968-1975 (Folder 29)
  - Mew, Melitta, 1983-1985 (Folder 30)
  - Meyer, Herman, 1946-1947 (Folder 31)
  - Meyer, Justus, 1946-1952 (Folder 32)
  - Meyer, William H., 1953 (Box 327, Folder 1)
  - Meyer-Abich, Klaus M., 1981-1982 (Folder 2)
  - Meyer-Bornsen, Christiane, 1982-1986 (Folder 3)
  - Meyer-Schwickerath, Gerd, n.d. (Folder 4)
  - Michaelis, Ernst, august, 1983 (Folder 5)
  - Michalos, Alex C., 1972 (Folder 6)
  - Michigan Quarterly Review, 1978-1979 (Folder 7)
  - Michl, Jan, 1979 (Folder 8)
  - Middelmann, Hans W., 1981-1983 (Folder 9)
  - Mieszkis, K. W., 1985 (Folder 10)
  - Miles, T. R., n.d. (Folder 11)
  - Milford-Hilferding, Peter, 1960-1984 (Folder 12)
  - Miller, David William and Farida.
    Includes David Miller's notes
    - Undated (Folder 13)
    - 1965-1966 (Folder 14)
    - 1967-1969 (Folder 15)
    - 1970-1973 (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - 1974-1979 (Folder 2)
    - 1980-1982 (Folder 3)
    - 1983 (Folder 4)
    - 1984. (Folder 5)
      Includes Karl Popper's notes
    - 1985-1986 (Folder 6)
  - Miller, Ian, 1983 (Box 329, Folder 1)
  - Milne, Alan J. M., 1947-1981 (Folder 2)
  - Mind (David W. Hamlyn), See also Ryle, Gilbert, 1971-1981. (Folder 3)
  - Mises, Richard von, 1935 (Folder 4)
  - Missimer, G., 1984 (Folder 5)
  - Mitchell, E. W. J., 1983 (Folder 6)
  - Mitchell, H. B., re translation of Karl Popper's interview "Les chemins de la verite", 1982 (Folder 7)
  - Mitchell, Peter, 1982 (Folder 8)
  - Mittelstrass, Jurgen, 1984 (Folder 9)
  - Mittwoch, Ursula, 1977 (Folder 10)
  - Moberly, Walter, 1951 (Folder 11)
  - Moewes, Winfried, 1980-1981 (Folder 12)
  - Moffat, James, 1969 (Folder 13)
  - Moir, David, 1982 (Folder 14)
  - Mokre, J., 1962 (Folder 15)
  - Moldauer, Peter, 1968 (Folder 16)
  - Molden, Fritz P., 1979-1980 (Folder 17)
  - Molden, Otto, 1948-1985 (Folder 18)
  - Mombert, Francois, 1979-1982 (Folder 19)
  - Mondadori (Anna Piana), 1975 (Folder 20)
  - Mondoperaio Edizione Avanti, 1979 (Folder 21)
  - Monist (Eugene Freeman), 1972-1982 (Folder 22)
  - Monod, Jacques, 1970-1975 (Folder 23)
  - Monod, Philippe, 1977-1979 (Folder 24)
  - Mont Pelerin Society (Friedrich A. von Hayek, A. Hunold), 1947-1979 (Folder 25)
  - Montague, Richard, 1960 (Folder 26)
  - Moorbath, Stephen, 1982 (Folder 27)
  - Moore, D. J., 1952 (Folder 28)
  - Moore, G. E., 1938-1958 (Folder 29)
  - Moore, Walter J., 1985 (Folder 30)
  - Moorhead, Hugh S., 1958 (Folder 31)
  - Morgan, Richard B., 1974-1979 (Folder 32)
  - Morgenstern, Oskar ( Mathematica ), 1973 (Folder 33)
  - Mori, I., 1971-1979 (Folder 34)
  - Morishige, Tsuchiya, 1984 (Folder 35)
  - Morl, Anton von, 1948 (Folder 36)
  - Morris, Charles W., 1936 (Folder 37)
  - Morris, Richard O., 1975 (Folder 38)
  - Morscher, Edgar, 1980-1981 (Folder 39)
  - Mosee, Margarete, n.d. (Folder 40)
  - Moser, Simon (osterreichisches College), 1950-1982 (Folder 41)
  - Moser-Duftner, Carin, 1979-1985 (Folder 42)
  - Moss, E. H. G., 1979 (Folder 43)
  - Motz, Hans, 1938-1983. (Box 330, Folder 1)
  - Mourelatos, Alexander P. D., 1974 (Folder 2)
  - Muckenheim, Wolfgang, 1984 (Folder 3)
  - Muller, Gert H., 1965-1980 (Folder 4)
  - Mugur-Schachter, Mioara, 1973-1983 (Folder 5)
  - Muhlmann, W. E., 1961 (Folder 6)
  - Mulligan, Kevin, 1979 (Folder 7)
  - Munch, Hans, 1970 (Folder 8)
  - Munro-Kerr, Anne (Society of Authors), 1976 (Folder 9)
  - Munz, Peter, 1946-1984 (Folder 10)
  - Murdoch, Professor, n.d. (Folder 11)
  - Murray, Gilbert, 1948 (Folder 12)
  - Murray, John Kerr, 1970-1971 (Folder 13)
  - Murray, W. A. Scott, 1980-1984 (Folder 14)
  - Musgrave, Alan, 1964-1981 (Folder 15)
  - Mycielski, Jan, n.d. (Folder 16)
  - Myddelton, David, 1979 (Folder 17)
  - Nadel, George H., 1959-1970 (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - Nagy, Lajos V., 1970 (Folder 2)
  - Naess, Arne, 1949-1964 (Folder 3)
  - Nahs, Hans-Georg, 1982-1983 (Folder 4)
  - Naik, V. A., 1980 (Folder 5)
  - Nalimov, Vassili V., 1971-1983 (Folder 6)
  - Naor, David, 1981 (Folder 7)
  - Nash, S. J., 1946 (Folder 8)
  - Nation (Carey McWilliams), 1954 (Folder 9)
  - National Bank Cultural Foundation (E. C. Casdaglis), 1982, re The Open Society (Folder 10)
  - National Campaign for the Abolition of Capital Punishment, 1961 (Folder 11)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities Fellowships, 1979 (Folder 12)